https://www.alchemie.com/privacy/

Sign Up
Search:
Search
Menu
Epoxy Resin GelcoatsLaminating ResinLaminating PasteModel PasteCasting ResinPolyurethane Resin Flexible / Rubber ResinHigh Strength Flexible ResinFastcast Unfilled ResinFastcast Filled ResinFoam Resin SystemsWater Clear ResinR.I.M. ResinVacuum Casting ResinResin for Electronics Epoxy ResinPolyurethane ResinModelboard MetaporPolyurethane Model boardEpoxy Model boardAdhesivesRTV Silicone Rubber Condensation CureSilicone Ancillary ProductsAddition CureAncillary Products Acrylic Polymer SystemsPolyester ResinPigmentsRelease / Sealing AgentsGlass Cloth ReinforcementFiller powdersAdhesivesSheetwaxFillet WaxProcessing MachinesAcetoneFlushing AgentIndustry AerospaceAgricultureAutomotiveBadge DomingCeramicsCompositesConcrete MouldingElectronicsFilm & TVFormula 1GiftwareHobbyInjection MouldingMarineModel MakingOil & GasPattern MakingRailRapid PrototypingApplications Air FiltersBack FillingBadge DomingBondingCarbon Prepreg ToolingCases for CeramicsChecking FixturesClear CastingCNC MillingCompositesConcrete MouldingCosmetic Carbon FibreElectrical EncapsulationElectrical PottingEmbeddingFace Casting - ConcreteFibrous PlasteringFoundry Patterns & Core BoxesHammer Form ToolsHand Lay Up / LaminatingJigs & FixturesLow Series ProductionMannequinsMaster PatternsModel MakingMould MakingNegatives and First ReproductionsOffshore and UnderseaPad PrintingPenny FlooringPlastic Injection Mould ToolsR.I.M Component PartsR.I.M. ToolingR.T.M. ToolsResin CastingResin InfusionRiver TablesRotacastingSanitaryware MouldsSheetmetal FormingSpin CastingStyling ModelsVacuum CastingVacuumforming and Thermoforming
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We understand that your privacy is important and we will treat any personal information you provide us as confidential and this will only be used and recorded in accordance with the Data Protection Act 2018. We promise to look after your personal information and we will not sell any information about you to any other party. Please also refer to our Cookie Policy.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
We will only collect information about you if you willingly provide it.  In order to do any of the following, you will need to provide us with certain details:
Place an order;
Sign up for emails;
Enter prize draws/competitions;
Take part in a survey (in this instance your details will be passed to a third party for research purposes); or
Give us feedback
The details you provide may include your name, email address, product selections, delivery address, telephone number, credit or debit card number, the card's expiry date and billing address. We will keep your personal information for as long as necessary and consistent with the purpose for which you have given it to us.
When you use this website, we may collect, store and use the following kinds of data:
Information about your PC and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of pages viewed to administer the website and improve the website and our services to you.
Information relating to any transactions carried out between you and Alchemie Ltd on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods and/or services. We will use this information to fulfill any order and to communicate with you when necessary.
Information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us and allowing us to send you email notifications and/or promotional information.
Information that you provide to us for the purpose of signing up for our email newsletters.
Personal data submitted to us will be used for the purposes specified in this section or as found elsewhere in the relevant parts of the website. We may use your personal information to:
Administer the website.
Improve your browsing experience by developing and improving the design and layout of the website, through monitoring your usage.
Process your orders; and
Provide you with information such as news regarding the website, new services and special offers or promotions that may be of interest to you via email, post or by mobile phone (also see 'keeping in touch with you' below).
DATA PROTECTION
Alchemie Ltd uses the latest in Secure Server Technology (SSL – 128bit encryption) to ensure that all of your personal and transactional information is protected to the highest standards. We never make your personal details available to companies outside Alchemie Ltd for marketing purposes, although our representatives and appointed agents and business partners may hold your data, so that your details and/or order can be processed and/or account maintained. Alchemie Ltd is registered with the Information Commissioners Office as a Data Controller. We will comply with the standard, procedures and requirements as laid down in the Data Protection Acts 2018 and to ensure that your personal data is kept secure and processed as required by the various laws in force from time-to-time.
REQUIRED INFORMATION - REGISTRATION OF PURCHASE FOR WARRANTY PURPOSES
For selected ranges available on the Alchemie.com Website, to ensure your manufacturer warranty is enabled, we may provide certain details to the manufacturer to facilitate this. We will only do this for warranties that require it, and for solely this purpose.
These details could include: Name, Address, Telephone Number, Email Address, and Product Purchased.We will notify you on each of our product listings which require us to submit your personal information. We will only use your provided information for this purpose, in relation to your order, and will be submitted securely. By placing your order with us, you consent to us registering your product on your behalf, to enable your Manufacturer Warranty. If you have any questions regarding this please contact us using our Contact Form or telephone 01926 641600.
COOKIES
When you enter this website, we will use cookies. Cookies are tiny text files that identify your computer to our server. These cookies in no way allow us access to your computer and do not store any details relating to you or your credit cards. They are used to record the areas of the site that you have visited and for how long, which provides us with useful usage information that helps us make our site more accessible to our users in line with their needs. The use of cookies helps us to improve the quality of service that we provide.
GOOGLE ANALYTICS
The following four Cookies are used by Google Analytics to store user behaviour on the site, including details such as pages visited, path through the site, length of time on each page, user location, and information on how you arrived at the website. We use this information to improve the website in accordance with user behaviour.
__utma
__utmb
__utmc
__utmz
These originate from www.google.com/analytics. You can read more about Google’s Analytics Privacy Policy at the Google Privacy and Terms page.
If you would like to opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across any website you visit, please visit Google Analytics Opt Out Page.
KEEPING IN TOUCH WITH YOU
We want to keep you up to date with key information about new ranges, promotional offers and what's coming soon to Alchemie.com via email, mobile phone or post.  We may also use your details to send you information, via email about other goods and services we sell or for research purposes. If you have registered to receive information from us, you can remove your contact details from our list by using the 'unsubscribe' links at the bottom of the promotional emails we send you or by responding to the text messages as indicated.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
POLICY AMENDMENTS
We may update our policies from time-time by posting a new version on our website, please check regularly to be aware of any updates. Please contact us using out contact form if you have any questions regarding this policy.
Contact
Alchemie Ltd
Warwick Road
Kineton
Warwick
CV35 0HU
United Kingdom
Contact Form
Coronavirus (COVID-19)
